Finding Dad is not the key.
The key is to find out if that woman
killed Chung.
What if she's connected to Chung's death?
She will be stripped of her right
of inheritance.
My wife didn't kill Chung B.
Hello, folks.
According to the record the Police
obtained from the smart watch company,
Mr. Cheung Siu-chung's heartbeat stopped
at 12:05 a.m. on October 16.
That means he was 21 years old when he died
and he was entitled to inherit
Mr. Cheung Kin-kwok's estate.
Therefore, the trust fund he set up
will take effect after the probate
is completed.
The allocation of assets is as follows...
Mr. Mok, when will I officially
become the owner of the house?
How soon will the trust fund take effect?
At least three months.
That long?
Mr. Cheung Siu-chung inherited
a huge estate.
It will take a while to process.
Do you have any questions?
Just make it quick.
I can't wait to spend the money.
Chung B was so sweet
to leave his mother such a generous gift.
Mr. Mok, I'm leaving if
there's nothing else.
Mr. Mok, I'm leaving too.
Hello? Yes, I need a taxi.
I can't watch that tramp inherit
the house without a fight.
Mr. Mok, can you tell me,
if Leung Yuet-ping did anything bad,
can she be disqualified
and won't get the money
or get the house?
What do you mean by anything bad?
What if she's connected to Chung's death?
If Mr. Cheung Siu-chung's death
was caused by Ms. Leung,
she will be stripped of her right
of inheritance.
Then I must follow her
and see if she was the killer.
Follow the taxi ahead.
Hey, don't lose it.
Hurry up, faster.
Run the light. I'll give you $500 more.
Is that necessary? The guy ran a red light.
Mother is following me?
She wants to find Chi.
Driver, let me off at the mall.
Stop the car.
Tai-di...
I saw you just now. But you kept going.
I was following that woman
hoping to find Chi.
Now she got away and there's no sign of her.
I know. I saw you.
Finding Dad is not the key.
The key is to find out if that woman
killed Chung.
Why would you think that?
Tell me, that night at the village house,
you shoved Chung and he fell, right?
Did he run into anything?
The glass cabinet.
Why do you ask?
At the mourning hall when you chased her,
she looked scared and what did she say?
Chung's head hit the cabinet because of you!
You shoved him into the glass cabinet.
You meant to kill him.
Glass cabinet?
She said she didn't go to the village house
How else would she know about
the glass cabinet?
Exactly! I was there and I know.
If she was never there,
how did she know about it?
She was lying.
That means she went to the village house.
She was connected to Chung's death!
It's possible. But we need proof.
That's what I intend to find out myself.
When I have enough,
I'll pass it to the Police.
What did you find out?
I left the law firm early, right?
I know that woman always calls for a taxi.
That's why I intend to start with the taxi.
But I saw you two come downstairs
one after another.
And you followed her in a taxi.
I didn't know what you intend to do,
then I saw you both got off the taxi.
So I decided to check out her taxi.
That's why I didn't brush you off.
But I didn't have time...
The customer wanted to go to Ho King Hotel
but she got out halfway there.
I see. What happened next?
I didn't exactly come back empty handed.
You're a good driver.
Better safe than sorry.
I always need a taxi,
can I call you directly?
You keep regular customers?
I don't take direct calls.
Here's my card.
Call the group chief if you need a ride.
He'll inform the group of drivers.
Whoever is closest to your location
will get the order.
I found out the woman may get
a different taxi each time.
So I posed as a regular customer
and called the group chief.
Hi, I called for a ride to Wan Mei Village
the other night.
When I got out of the car,
I left an important letter behind.
I need to contact the driver.
When? October 15...
between 11p.m. and midnight.
Yes...
I'll leave you my number.
Please call me back ASAP.
Did you hear from the driver?
Not yet. It's a long shot anyway.
If the driver calls back,
then it means Leung Yuet-ping
was at the village house
and she may be connected to Chung's death.
You suspected me before,
why are you telling me this?
Why do you think I suspect you?
I saw you going through my things.
Yes, I checked your phone
because I wanted to find a picture.
Since you already know,
can I borrow it and look at the picture?
Why didn't you just ask me? Here.
Why sneak around and go through my phone?
I barely know you. Can't ask you directly.
Here...look at this.
Why are you showing me the picture?
The jacket.
The Police found it in your room
I get a feeling something was not right.
Then I finally remembered.
Look at the edge, it had a row of pearls.
But the one the Police found did not.
No wonder!
The first time I wanted to toss it,
Chi caught me in the act.
I threw it away the second time,
but the Police found it again.
It wasn't even the same one.
Go show that to the Police.
Not yet. This isn't enough.
Besides, I only took a glance.
I can't be sure I didn't see it wrong.
Anyway, at least you care enough
to do something about it.
Unlike the others who made me out
to be a vicious murderer.
I know you loved Chung very much.
Even without this picture,
I don't believe you'd kill him.
When I was looking for you
on Tap Tung Island,
a villager told me
someone was looking into
giving her grandson a burial at sea.
I knew it was you right away.
A lot happened these past few months.
My husband and my daughter-in-law
had an affair,
my grandson was not my grandson
and wanted to fight me for the inheritance.
As the wife of the village chief,
I became a murder suspect.
The villagers doubted me,
my cousin Nam and Chau, my maid
of over 20 years betrayed me.
But my granddaughter, who has
never been close to me,
understood the injustice
and offered to help me.
Life can be so unpredictable.
In this house, Chung was closest to me.
Now that he's gone,
I guess he would have been worried
about you and Dad the most.
I will help you watch over them.
The taxi driver still hasn't called back.
Let me call the group chief and
get his number.
Hello?
Driver, I'm a regular customer
of your taxi group.
On the night of October 15,
you took me to Wan Mei Village.
I did not. Is this a scam?
No, the group chief checked
the orders that night.
He said it was you and gave me
your number.
Say no more. You're an imposter.
How rude of him!
You were supposed to be a regular customer.
He knew I was an imposter
as soon as he picked up the phone.
Did he see through me?
How come?
He'll know if he called that woman directly.
Rats! I overlooked that.
We have no more leads?
Luckily, the driver called me.
Hello, I'm the driver of WK206.
Are you the customer who
went to Wan Mei Village?
I checked the car,
I didn't find any letter you left behind.
What are you talking about?
Who are you calling?
Didn't you call the taxi group
and said you rode with me to Wan Mei Village
and left something in my car
and wanted to find the driver?
That was me.
No, I didn't make any calls.
Can you tell me exactly what happened?
Someone called the group
about October 15 between
11p.m. and midnight,
from Ko Cho Village to Wan Mei Village,
she left something important in my car
and wanted to find the driver.
That's me.
But the Chief left out a digit when
he wrote down the phone number.
So he told me to look up the order
and call you back.
It wasn't you?
But she was very clear on the details
of that night.
Maybe it was someone I know.
What number did she leave?
It only has seven digits.
It's OK, just give it to me.
5151953...
(Tai-di)
OK...sorry, this is someone I know.
But she has mental problems
and is a stalker.
She's checking up on me and harassing me.
Do me a favor, if she calls back,
please don't tell her anything about me.
I'm worried about my safety.
Oh dear! OK, I know what to do.
Thanks, pal.
Try to track me down? Think again.
Who is it?
Don't open the door until you
see who it is.
Mom, I missed you! Mom...
Chi.
I missed you all.
Are you scared?
We found you even though you're hiding.
Tai-di...
Lam, I'm not coming.
The customer wanted to go to Ho King Hotel
but got off halfway there.
Luckily, Tai-di remembered the driver
mentioned Ho King Hotel.
You think you can ditch me?
Mother and child have an inseparable link.
I can always find him wherever you take him.
So what if you can find him?
Let's see how you take him away.
Dad, the coffee shop has the best
vanilla sundae.
Shall we go down for afternoon tea and talk?
Good! I want that.
Let's go down now.
It's not that hard.
Chi, why did you leave without a word?
I've been calling you
and your phone is turned off.
Do you know how much I missed you?
I wanted to call you too. But I can't.
I know that.
Let's go home after you finish eating.
You know how much I missed you?
The way you run off like that,
do you want to kill me?
I can't.
Why not? Someone won't let you?
I just can't.
Dad, how long do you want to stay here?
A month.
What?
I saw the hotel has a promotion.
If you stay for a month,
you can book the Presidential Suite.
Dad, you were being the good son
and knew Grandma likes the palace
style design in the Presidential Suite,
that's why you want to stay a month
and let Grandma stay there for a day?
Oops! They knew. No more surprises.
Chi, I know you're a filial son.
I don't care if I get to stay in the hotel,
as long as I can see you every day,
I don't mind living in a partitioned flat.
Come home with me, OK?
I just can't.
Why not?
Go ahead. Tell them.
Honey is having a baby.
What?
If she's not leaving, I'm not leaving.
I need to learn to take care of
the teddy bear,
so I can look after the baby later.
Well? There'll be someone else
to look after Chi.
Aren't you happy? Surprised?
This baby is Chung B.
He wants to be my son again.
Tummy ache. I need to use the toilet.
I'll go with you.
You think it's real?
I think it's her excuse.
She wants Chi to stay here
and won't let him go home.
Something is fishy.
I agree.
But we can't let Dad stay here indefinitely.
We must find a way to verify
if that woman is pregnant.
She left the room key. I'll search the room.
Look for name cards of gynecologists,
napkins or pregnancy tests...
I will.
Wait, Grandma...
Is it one line or two lines?
Don't you know? How can you be a lawyer?
Let me do it.
Where's Mother?
Since Dad has stomachache,
she went out to get him meds.
I'll get the bill.
Sorry, afternoon tea hours are up.
Can you settle the bill?
Didn't my wife pay for it?
Hello, Tai-di?
Grandma, get out! She's coming.
Why did you sneak into my room?
What are you looking for?
Are you scared? What are you hiding?
You probably suspect I'm faking my pregnancy
and came up to look for any proof
to expose me
and drive a wedge between me and Chi.
So what if I am?
You were afraid I'll get answers from Chi.
That's why you moved out in a hurry.
A fake pregnancy is a lousy idea.
You must have a lot to hide.
I will expose you.
I won't let you get away with it.
You're no match for me!
We'll see.
Ouch...
Get me an ambulance!
Do I have Leung Yuet-ping's family?
I'm her husband.
The patient and the baby are fine.
But since the baby is only two weeks old,
the mother should be very careful
early in the pregnancy.
She does not need to be hospitalized
but should be off her feet this week
and stop running around.
Thank you.
Honey, are you OK?
I'm fine. The doctor said the baby is OK.
Hear that? She's not lying.
She's really carrying Chi's baby?
I've had enough after all these years.
I just didn't expect you to hate me so much
you want to hurt your grandchild.
Dad, let's go home and talk
and sort things out, OK?
I'm not going. I'm not going!
I'm staying to watch Honey and the baby.
I told you I didn't shove her. She lied.
You must believe me.
You shoved her. You're the baddie.
I don't want to see you. Leave...
Go away...
I did not...
Are you OK?
Go! I don't like you. Go away...
Dad is in a rage. Nothing you say will help.
Let's go home, OK?
I don't want to see you.
OK...don't be upset.
That tramp is so calculating.
She's always setting a trap for me.
What should I do? Chi is angry with me.
That's why we must hurry and find
proof she was at the village house.
It's the only way to clear your name.
More importantly, let Dad know
who's the real baddie
so he'll come home with us.
Let's see when she'll show her cloven hoof.
When you went to her room,
did you find anything suspicious?
I found a card of a detective agency.
(Henry Wong Detective Agency)
I took a picture of it.
I wonder why she hired a private detective.
To check on Chung?
Let's go find out.
Let's pay the private detective.
Ask him what that tramp wanted.
They have rules about protecting
the client's privacy
and probably signed a
non-disclosure agreement.
Paying him won't make him talk.
Then what?
Hire this guy to check up on me.
Then I'll pretend to catch him following me
and take pictures of him.
Then we post the pictures online
and accuse him of being unprofessional
so he'll never work again.
That's not enough.
I need to bluff him.
According to Section 160 of
Cap 200 Crimes Ordinance,
"if any person loiters in a public place
or in the common parts of any building
and his presence there, causes any person
reasonably to be concerned for his safety,
the maximum penalty is imprisonment for
six months and a fine of $10,000.
Wow, you're worthy of being a lawyer,
you know the law by heart.
Can I help you?
I'm looking for Henry Wong.
That's me.
You?
Please come in.
My office is over here.
Please have a seat and talk.
How can I help you?
Your husband is having an affair?
He has a mistress stashed up somewhere
or he's giving her a monthly allowance?
Check on her.
OK, the mistress.
No. She's my granddaughter.
I suspect a man is sponging off her.
Go find out.
No problem. I'll open a file for you.
Honey, have some tea.
Are you tired?
A little.
Pregnant women will get cramps.
How do you know?
You were like that when you had Chung B.
But don't worry. I'll be with you.
I can do anything.
My legs are fine, but not my heart.
You're not feeling well?
Mom said you must go to the hospital
if you're not feeling well.
Don't listen to her, you must listen to me.
I don't feel good
because even though I get the house,
you and your mother can stay there
till you pass away.
I'm worried.
About what?
I know you love me and the baby.
But what will your mother do to us?
How about that? After Chung's trust fund
becomes effective,
tell your mother to move out.
What?
I'm afraid the baby will be born
without a father.
Your mother only wanted you
to go home with her.
She obviously wanted to separate us.
Then...we can stay here.
I will protect you and the baby.
But I don't want to live in a hotel
for the rest of my life.
That's true.
It's hard to live with someone.
If we don't live together,
I won't be fighting with your mother.
She can always visit the baby.
So I have to live apart from Mom?
I have never done that before.
Let's rent a house nearby for her.
You can go there and visit her.
Chung's trust fund gave her
a monthly allowance of $50K.
You're such a filial son, give her your $30K
and she'll have $80K a month.
That's a lot of money, right?
Yes, Mom should be happy she has money
to buy things she likes to eat.
That's why, you must convince her
to move out.
Or else I'll move out with the baby
and you'll never see us again.
No...I want to play with the baby.
That's why you must listen to me, OK?
I know.
Very good.
What is it?
What are you doing here?
You complain I don't take good enough
care of Chi.
Now, I'm doing my best.
Honey...
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, open the door!
Chi...
Honey...
Hey...
Go away!
Chi...
No way! Why don't I ever win the lottery?
This is what I get.
(Terminate pregnancy)
Honey, we're having a baby?
You know how to read the pregnancy test?
Mom taught me.
Two red lines means there's a baby.
We're having a baby.
Go away! You're good for nothing else.
I wonder if it's a boy or a girl.
Let me listen.
Hello! Are you a boy or a girl?
Honey, you're back.
I want to talk to you...
Be quiet. I bought you this.
Take care of it like it was a baby.
Wow! I want to know...
Stop asking me anything.
Pregnant women are irritable.
OK.
Hello? How are you? My name is Chi.
(What are the procedures to terminate
my pregnancy?)
Someone called the group
about October 15 between
11p.m. and midnight,
from Ko Cho Village to Wan Mei Village,
she left something important in my car...
(Tai-di)
Tai-di is beginning to suspect me.
Though I asked the driver not to
disclose anything,
they'll eventually find a way.
Better keep this bargaining chip
to drive a wedge between them.
I should get the money soon.
I'll deal with them later.
Grandma, did you tell her the time?
I don't see anyone following me.
I told her clearly
I overheard you on the phone,
you're meeting the sponge at
3 o'clock at Pier No. 9.
Is it possible she's here but
we can't see her?
Is she using a drone camera?
No way. I've been watching the whole time.
It's not a man. It's a tomboy.
Mrs. Cheung, this is your granddaughter's
sponge boyfriend.
He's not meeting with your granddaughter,
but taking another girl to Macau.
I will follow him.
But I charge more for a job
outside Hong Kong.
I'll give you a quote later.
Take a look at the pictures
and pay me the balance.
What? She's making this up!
Let's go find her.
Good.
Feed her! Yes...look sweet!
You must smile more.
You're crazy about her
and you're hitting on her.
Yes...smile!
Henry Wong...you asked someone
to pose as the sponge?
My granddaughter doesn't know this guy.
You're caught red-handed for conning me.
No, maybe I followed the wrong guy.
Stop lying! There's no sponge.
You couldn't have made a mistake.
You set me up?
We have pictures of you.
One, you let us track you so easily,
you're very unprofessional.
Two, you asked someone to pose as
the target and took pictures,
you're scamming the client.
We'll post this online.
Make sure we have her picture.
Whether she's Charlie Lau or William Man,
she'll never get another job.
Please don't. Henry Wong is my uncle.
I work for him.
But he suddenly fell off the grid
and the other employees left.
I had no choice but to take your case.
I didn't mean to scam you.
My uncle didn't pay my salary,
I was forced to do this.
No wonder there was no one else
at the agency.
Please go easy on me.
I have mouths to feed.
I'll refund your money.
You know what cases your uncle worked on?
Of course! I helped him on every case.
OK, we can go easy on you.
But you must sell us something.
I didn't expect that tramp
to hire someone to follow Chung
and she found out about the trust fund.
I bet she was pissed she didn't get
all of Chung's money
and Chi and I will live in the house
until we die.
What?
Let's go to the Police
and ask them to find the evidence
to arrest that tramp.
The jacket they found wasn't mine.
Grandma, what's wrong? Are you feeling OK?
I feel dizzy and weak...
Oh dear! You're having a stroke? Sit down...
I'll get you an ambulance.
Be careful. Hang on...
No need.
What?
Just take me somewhere.
You feel dizzy because of low blood sugar.
Does the honey lemon make you feel better?
Yes!
You can't read a pregnancy test.
You have so little common sense.
How did you become a lawyer?
You don't need to know that to be a lawyer.
The elderly cannot go hungry.
I know now. Let's eat.
Have a thigh.
Let's eat...
Chi, here's a thigh for you.
Thanks, Mom.
Chung, one for you too.
Thanks, Grandma.
Good boy!
Grandma...have some veggies.
Good! You should eat more.
Yes, have some chicken.
The sweet and sour pork is good too.
Sze Sir, what do you think of
the information Cheung Tai-di gave us?
If Tang Suk-han was set up,
someone wanted us to find the jacket
to prove Tang Suk-han was at the scene.
Someone who knew Tang Suk-han wore
the jacket to identify the body.
Leung Yuet-ping volunteered to tell us
Tang Suk-han tossed the jacket
the day after Cheung Siu-chung died
and that Tang Heung-nam drove
Tang Suk-han to the village house.
Her goal was to get us to
investigate Tang Suk-han.
It's likely Leung Yuet-ping planted
the evidence.
Tang Suk-han said the friend who gave her
the jacket already passed away.
Where else can we look?
The jacket had no label.
We have no idea where it was sold.
Did you notice their clothes have
something in common?
One is in her 40s, the other in her 60s.
They should have different tastes.
What kind of handbags do they use?
Designer brand.
You mean they are expensive
designer jackets?
We can find designer handbags online,
but these jackets had no labels.
It's hard to trace.
Tang Suk-han's jacket may be hard to trace.
If Leung Yuet-ping planted the evidence,
she must know where to buy it.
Exactly! Something expensive
but had no label,
what are the possibilities?
A local designer?
Hey! Didn't they put sugar?
Thanks, Brother Bo! Get to work.
OK.
I designed both jackets.
From choosing the fabric, tailoring
and sewing,
I did it all by myself.
I added pearls as details on one of them,
along the hem and the pocket opening.
And the other one doesn't.
They're both one of a kind.
Can you give us the details of the buyer?
Sure.
It was more than a year back.
Here...the one with the pearls,
I sold it to a granny
who said it was a gift for a friend.
She paid cash for it.
The other was sold to a lady
who paid with a credit card.
The cardholder's name is Leung Yuet-ping.
Chung's head hit the cabinet because of you!
You shoved him into the glass cabinet.
You meant to kill him.
Henry Wong said she helped Leung Yuet-ping
track down Cheung Siu-chung,
she knew about the trust fund
and Cheung Siu-chung was in Hunghom.
Hunghom? He went to Tang Heung-nam's
coffin shop?
I think so too.
Leung Yuet-ping probably went to see
Cheung Siu-chung at the coffin shop.
But Tang Heung-nam said nothing about this.
A few days before he died,
did Cheung Siu-chung see you here?
No.
Did you step out and didn't know about it?
I don't think so.
Hey, Shing!
What?
Did my godson come by?
I know him. He came on October 14.
Why do you remember it was October 14?
Of course! I fought with my wife that day
and she threatened to divorce me.
Can you tell us what happened?
He came to see Brother Nam that day.
I said Brother Nam stepped out
and told him to come back later.
But he didn't come back.
(The day before the incident)
I saw him run into a woman outside
and they started talking.
Then my wife called me.
She wanted a divorce,
obviously, I was eager to coax her
so I didn't hear what they said.
Can you describe the woman?
I only took a glance.
Tall and slender, in her 40s.
She was quite a looker.
Is that her?
I think so.
Senior Constable Sze King, Crime Unit,
New Territories East.
Officer Cheung Yau-ming.
What is it, Officers?
Ms. Leung Yuet-ping, we suspect you're
connected to Cheung Siu-chung's death.
We need you to facilitate our investigation.
Why are you arresting my wife?
Ms. Leung, according to your last statement,
at 9p.m. on October 15,
you and your husband Cheung Wang-chi
were already in bed.
We also need Mr. Cheung to help
facilitate our investigation.
What?
Where's my husband?
Relax. Our colleagues are with him.
We wish to take your statement.
On October 15, between 10:45p.m.
and 12:30a.m. on October 16,
which was Cheung Siu-chung's time of death,
did you go to Wan Mei Village?
I already told you,
my husband and I were asleep at home.
We checked the surveillance cameras
from Ko Cho Village to Wan Mei Village,
we saw a taxi with the license plate WK206
came out of Ko Cho Village.
We followed this taxi,
it got onto Man Nin Street
and then went to Wan Mei Village.
We checked, the taxi got onto Man Nin Street
and stopped in front of a convenience store.
According to our record, you went
inside the convenience store
because you paid with your member app.
The salesclerk also confirmed
you boarded WK206 and left.
You claimed you never went to
Cheung Siu-chung's village house,
then how come we heard you
at the mourning hall
accusing Tang Suk-han of shoving
Cheung Siu-chung into the glass cabinet?
If you were never there,
how did you know there was
a glass cabinet?
I don't recall saying that.
We compared the jacket found in
Tang Suk-han's room
with the pictures she took when she
wore it to a gathering.
We noticed it was a different jacket.
Hers had pearl trimmings.
The one found in her room did not.
Both jackets were made by Joyce Lee,
a local designer.
We checked, you bought one of them
with your credit card.
We have reasons to suspect
you knew Tan Suk-han went to
the village house that night
and wore that jacket to identify the body,
so you planted your jacket in her room
to mislead the Police into thinking
Tang Suk-han killed Cheung Siu-chung.
Separately, we also found out,
after Cheung Siu-chung ran away from home,
you hired a private detective
to track him down.
That's why before Cheung Siu-chung died,
you already knew about the trust fund.
Near Tang Heung-nam's coffin shop in Hunghom
a staff member confirmed you had an
argument with Cheung Siu-chung.
We have reasons to believe
you were not happy with Cheung Siu-chung's
allocation of the assets,
you went to the village house to kill him
and took the second document
of the trust fund.
I admit I saw Chung at the village house
to persuade him to re-allocate
the assets in the trust fund.
But he wouldn't listen to me.
I was so angry I left.
He was still alive when I left.
I didn't say anything before,
because I was afraid you'd suspect me.
I want to see my wife...
Calm down...take a deep breath! Sit down.
I need to see my wife...
I must see my wife...
Calm down...Calm down, Sir!
Please calm down...
Please sit back down...
Kwan Sir! Lee Sir!
Something wrong with this guy...
What's wrong? Hold him down...
Why did you put the jacket
in Tang Suk-han's room?
Sze Sir, Cheung Wang-chi clutched his heart
and complained about chest pain.
We called an ambulance to
take him to the hospital.
I need to see my husband.
Not now.
No, he has the mental age of an 8-year-old.
He has never been to a Police station,
he must be terrified.
Is he having a heart attack?
He could die! Please let me see him.
Only I can calm him down.
Please, Sir!
OK, we'll go with her.
Call his family. Maybe they can watch him.
We'll finish taking your statement later.
Thank you.
We have examined Cheung Wang-chi. He's fine.
But he's emotionally unstable
and kept saying he had chest pain.
So we took him to the ward for
further examinations.
Take me to my wife. I want to see my wife...
Mr Cheung...
I don't want to see you.
Tell them to leave.
I don't want to see them.
Sir, please lie down, OK?
Calm down...
Sze Sir, Cheung Sir, my husband
is emotionally unstable.
Can you step outside
and let me calm him down?
Don't do this...
No! Go away...I don't want to see them...
OK...they're gone.
It's OK, I'm here...
Sir, how is my son?
He seems to have calmed down.
I want to see him.
Sure.
Chi!
Dad!
My wife didn't kill Chung B.
I did.
What?